<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dark Entropy</title><link>https://darkentropy.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Dark Entropy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://darkentropy.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tier 4 Cleared!</title><link>https://darkentropy.github.io/posts/tier4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darkentropy.github.io/posts/tier4/</guid><description>Tier 4 Content Cleared! Congrats to Dark Entropy for clearing all of tier 4!
Kara cleared June 6th, with Nigthbane killed on June 12th. Gruul cleared June 7th. Magtheridon cleared (night 1 of attempts) June 17th. Congrats to all raiders - we&amp;rsquo;re off to a fantastic start! Let&amp;rsquo;s get the whole guild decked out to roll into T5 and smash up TK and SSC!</description></item><item><title>Raid Setup</title><link>https://darkentropy.github.io/posts/raid/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darkentropy.github.io/posts/raid/</guid><description>Core Raid Team Dark Entropy&amp;rsquo;s core raid is intended to be a quasi-competitive raid group. Guild members who are part of this raid group will need to earn their keep, and are expected to be consistent performers who show up prepared, work as a team, and are able to constructively help others. The composition of this raid, and the raiders therein, will be dependent on guild needs and are based on performance over FOTM.</description></item><item><title>Guild Charter</title><link>https://darkentropy.github.io/posts/guildcharter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darkentropy.github.io/posts/guildcharter/</guid><description>Dark Entropy&amp;rsquo;s Mission Statement Dark Entropy aims to provide a fun, welcoming atmosphere and serious raiding environment for our players.
Our goal is to clear all current content as rapidly as is reasonably possible upon release and to be competetive in progression with the top guilds on our server.
The guild consists largely of old friends from early retail WoW. We want to provide a friendly environment and home for all of our players, but participation in the core raid team will be based exclusively on class/role needs and performance.</description></item><item><title>Loot System</title><link>https://darkentropy.github.io/posts/loot/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darkentropy.github.io/posts/loot/</guid><description>Dark Entropy Loot System Dark Entropy uses a Loot Council system for loot distribution in 25-man content.
Loot will be distributed by the officers as seen fit.
Loot distribution will be based on a variety of factors including but not limited to:
Performance in raids Preparedness Attendance Conduct Raid needs (e.g. tank gear prio) We make an effort to provide a reasonable level of transparency to the Loot Council process.</description></item></channel></rss>